httpool.com 2009-02-18

# Privacy policy - Httpool Online Advertising

**Before you are regulations, governing protection of privacy and personal information and data (Privacy Policy), that are collected from the website by Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH, Taborstraße 7/8, 1020 Vienna, Austria (“controller”).**

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy does not apply for other websites displayed as links from within our services. These other sites may use various means to try to collect personal information from you. 

Please read provisions stated below carefully and only than accepted them as requested. When accepting this Privacy Policy you give your informed personal consent that your personal information and data can be collected, processed and transferred to other countries for specific reasons and under conditions as stated below. 

**Information provided by the user**

When a user signs up to the website that requires registration, various interactive applications ask him to submit personal information as follows: 

  * name and surname
  * e-mail address
  * telephone number
  * fax number

For certain services it is necessary for a user to create his users account which will enable him to use certain applications. In these cases user is asked to submit personal information an data as follows: 

Personal information: 

  * type of user (natural / legal person)
  * name of the company
  * name and surname

Contact information: 

  * address, area code and city
  * telephone number
  * fax number
  * e-mail address

Payment information: 

  * type of payment account
  * number of payment account
  * tax number
  * registrar number of the company
  * information on the profit, submitted using special payment application filled out by user

User name: 

  * Encrypted user password

Above mentioned information is needed to ensure mutual cooperation and services to users including access to the application, display of customized content and advertising; communications with users, transfer of profit deriving from online advertising; ensuring the technical functioning of the network; research and analysis in order to maintain and protect our services. 

**Cookies:**

When you visit a website or are viewing certain advertisements on the web, your computer is sent at least one cookie, a small file containing a string of characters, which can identify a user. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Cookies are also used to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. 

**IP address:**

When you access our services, our server automatically records your IP address that enables us to identify the location of the computer used to access certain websites. This is used to improve the quality of our services and manage ads across the web. 

Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH only collects and processes personal information and data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. All personal information and data is stored and processed on a secured server owned by Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH. Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH has taken special care to secure personal information and data using adequate organizational and technical procedures and actions that enable us to prevent involuntary or voluntary unauthorized access, processing, destruction, alternation or loss of information.. Personal information and data is not shared with other users or processors except in cases where adequate contracts are concluded with processors, companies registered to conduct such activities that guarantee adequate procedures and actions prescribed by the law. We occasionally share personal information and data with our affiliated companies or persons otherwise linked with our company, providing us with various supporting services abroad (countries inside as well as outside European Union) to give you more complete and quality services. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and other appropriate legal measures. Access to personal information and data is restricted to specially authorized employees and contractors that need to know that information in order to operate, develop and improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. Personal information and data can also be shared in cases of violations or other demands deriving from any applicable law or regulation. Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH does not collect or process sensitive personal information. Personal information and data is kept and stored only for the period of time needed to fulfill the purpose for which they were collected and processed. After the purpose is fulfilled all personal information and data is deleted or otherwise blocked. 

Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH is for purposes of its direct marketing allowed to use information of the persons name, surname, address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address. Direct marketing means offering of goods and services, employment or temporary jobs by using postal services, telephone calls, e-mails or other telecommunication services. If Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH intends to share above mentioned information with other users for purposes of direct marketing, he must first inform the person in question of his intent and acquire his consent prior to sharing of information. Any person may at any time request in writing that his personal information is no more used for purposes of direct marketing. 

Collector must, upon a written request of the person whose personal information and data is being collected and processed, submitted to the collector under legal conditions, provide access to his personal information, give confirmation on whether such information is being processed, deliver excerpts of such information and allow this person to copy such information as well as provide the person with information on sharing of his personal information together with grounds and purpose of such sharing. Collector must also give information on the source of personal information and data, on the method and purpose of processing of information as well as give other explanations as requested by the law. 

Collector must, upon a written request of the person whose personal information and data is being collected and processed, submitted to the collector under legal conditions, correct insufficient or inaccurate data, as well as delete or block data that has been proven by the person in question to be insufficient, inaccurate, outdated or collected and processed contrary to the law. Collector must also upon request inform all users with whom such information was shared of such correction, deletion or blockage of these information. Collector can deny such requests if they are unfunded or would require substantial costs, effort or time. 

If you have any additional questions about this Privacy Policy or you have certain requests or complaints regarding data protection, please address us in writing at: 

Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH  
Taborstraße 7/8  
1020 Vienna  
Austria

When a written request or complaint is received, we will contact you and try to settle the matter to our mutual satisfaction. 

Respectfully  
Httpool Internet Marketing GmbH
